A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Education, 2001-2010 (bulk 2005-2009)
Library of Virginia
- II. Constituent Correspondence, 2006-2010., Extent: 8.0 cubic feet (8 boxes). (Box 7-14)
  Correspondence from 2009, additional correspondence from 2006 to 2008 as well as correspondence submitted via email can be found in boxes 13 and 14. These records do not appear to have been entered into the database and do not have a tracking number. Researchers interested in a particular topic or agency should also utilize Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, Assigned State Agencies, and Series III. Office of the Secretary because they contain correspondence as well as supporting documentation.
  This series has been processed using minimal processing standards: the original arrangement has been maintained, the container list is brief and simple, and the records have not been refoldered and fasteners have not been removed.
  This series may contain restricted material and must be reviewed by archival staff before being used.
  - 2567932 - 2620265, 2006. (Box 7)
  - 2620307 - 2676205, 2006-2007. (Box 8)
  - 2676463 - 2718772, 2007-2008. (Box 9)
  - 2718630 - 2744355, 2008. (Box 10)
  - 2740968 - 2764546, 2008. (Box 11)
  - 2764657 - 2790007, 2008. (Box 12)
  - Constituent email and letter responses not in IQ database, 2006-2009. (Box 13)
  - Constituent email and letter responses not in IQ database, 2008-2010. (Box 14)
- III. Office of the Secretary, 2001-2009 (bulk 2006-2009)., Extent: 9.96 cubic feet (22 boxes). (Box 15-35; 53)
  The Office of the Secretary series is housed in 22 boxes and is arranged into five subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Files of Secretary of Education Thomas R. Morris, 2001-2003; 2006-2009 (bulk 2006-2008); B. Files of Judy Heiman, Deputy Secretary of Education, 2003-2007 (bulk 2006); C. Files of Dietra Trent, Deputy Secretary of Education, 2005-2009; D. Files of Jean Bankos, Senior Advisor to the Governor for Educational Projects, 2001-2002; 2004-2009 (bulk 2006-2008); and E. Files of Kendall Tyree, Special Assistant to the Secretary of Education, 2002; 2005-2007. The series consists of agendas, agreements, briefing binders, correspondence, handouts, memorandum, notes, presentations, and reports.
  Some of the notable correspondence in this series relates to the following topics: No Child Left Behind, Tuition Assistant Grant Program (TAG), education funding, Standards of Learning (SOL), Standards of Quality (SOQ), budget cuts in state aid to public libraries, early childhood education, Start Strong Council, college financial aid, teacher salaries, Small, Women, and Minority-Owned Business Program (SWAM), P-16 Education Council, and campus security.
  This series has been processed using minimal processing standards: most of the original arrangement has been maintained and the container list is brief and simple.
  - Subseries III.A. Files of Secretary Thomas R. Morris, 2001-2003; 2006-2009 (bulk 2006-2008)., Extent: 3.63 cubic feet (9 boxes).
    This subseries is housed in 9 boxes and is further divided into chronological and subject files. The chronological files contains copies of out-going correspondence from the Secretary of Education. They were maintained by the executive assistant to the secretary. Some of these records may be duplicated in Series II. Constituent Correspondence. Correspondence between May 2008 and December 2008 are not extant. The subject files were housed in Secretary Morris' office and have no apparent order. The subject files include conference/forum/meeting materials, reports, and correspondence. Thomas R. Morris served as Secretary of Education from January 2006 to January 2010.
    Some of the notable records in this series relates to the following topics: No Child Left Behind, Tuition Assistant Grant Program (TAG), education funding, Standards of Learning (SOL), Standards of Quality (SOQ), budget cuts in state aid to public libraries, early childhood education, Start Strong Council, college financial aid, teacher salaries, Small, Women, and Minority-Owned Business Program (SWAM), P-16 Education Council, and campus security.
    - Chronological
      - 2006 January 19 - 2006 February 28 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - 2006 March 2 - 2006 April 20 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - 2006 April 24 - 2006 May 30 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - 2006 June 2 - 2006 July 10 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - 2006 July 13 - 2006 August 10 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - 2006 August 10 - 2006 September 5 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - 2006 September 11 - 2006 October 31 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - 2006 November 2 - 2006 December 5 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - 2006 December 5 - 2006 December 20 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - 2006 December 20 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - 2006 December 20 - 2006 December 28 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - 2007 January 9 - 2007 February 23 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - 2007 February 23 - 2007 March 19 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - 2007 March 19 - 2007 April 27 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - 2007 May 1 - 2007 June 14 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - 2007 June 18 - 2007 July 31 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - 2007 August 1 - 2007 August 27 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - 2007 September 5 - 2007 October 31 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - 2007 November 1 - 2007 December 20 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - 2008 January 2 - 2008 January 28 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 2008 January 28 - 2008 February 11 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - 2008 February 12 - 2008 March 10 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - 2008 March 11 - 2008 April 15 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - 2008 April 16 - 2008 April 30 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - 2008 May 1 to 2008 December 31 not extant.
      - 2009 January 5 - 2009 January 27. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - 2009 January 28 - 2009 February 11. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - 2009 February 12 - 2009 December 23. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files
      - Auditor of Public Accounts Reports, 2007-2009. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Auditor of Public Accounts Reports, 2007-2008. (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Reports, 2008. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - SWAM Reports, 2008 October-2008 December. (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Department of Education Memos, 2005; 2007-2008. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Tuition Moderation Incentive Fund, 2008. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - State Managed Shelter Initiative, 2008. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Energy Plan, 2008. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - P-16 Education Council Meeting, 2008 February 19. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Early Childhood Foundation Board Member Handbook, 2007 April 25. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - National Math and Science Initiative, Virginia Advanced Study Strategy, Board of Directors Handbook, 2007. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Eastern Virginia Medical School, The Virginia Modeling and Simulation Initiative (VIMSIM), Report to General Assembly, 2008 October 1. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - State Board for Community Colleges, Meeting Book, 2008 September 18. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - State Board for Community Colleges, Meeting Book, 2008 November 13. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - At-Risk Student Workshop, Virginia Student Services Conference (VSSC), 2008 November 21. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 2008. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Virginia Critical Infrastructure Protection and Resiliency Strategic Plan, 2008 May 8. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Analysis of Virginia Unemployment and Community College Enrollment Trends, 2008. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Military Institute Financial Statements for the Year Ended 30 June 2008, 2008 October. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Common Wealth: College Learning and Virginia's Shared Future, 2008 November 18. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Comprehensive Agreement for Hotel Conference Center, George Mason University, Fairfax Campus, 2008 July (part 1 of 3). (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Comprehensive Agreement for Hotel Conference Center, George Mason University, Fairfax Campus, 2008 July (part 2 of 3). (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Comprehensive Agreement for Hotel Conference Center, George Mason University, Fairfax Campus, 2008 July (part 3 of 3). (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - McIntire-Stennis Cooperative Foresty Act of 2009 (Virginia Tech and Virginia State University), 2009. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Federal Stimulus Package, 2009. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - 2009 General Assembly Session, 2009. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Cooperative Marketing and Advertising Initiatives, 2008-2009. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Circuit City Bankruptcy Court, 2009. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Petersburg Schools, undated. (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) Letters for Governor's Signature, 2009. (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - College of Independent Colleges in Virginia, Tuition Assistance Grant (TAG), 2006. (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Student Risk Assessment and Counseling Conference, 2008 April 22. (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Education Issues, 2001-2003. (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Henrico County Public Schools, Professional Growth Plan, undated. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Virginia School Boards Association, 2006 Showcases for Success, 2006. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Higher Education Bill Signing, 2008 May 29. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Carl Perkins Career and Technical Education, 2007 August 1. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - American Civil War Center at Historic Tredegar, 2006; 2008. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Planned Parenthood, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Exemplary Physical Education Curriculum (EPEC), 2006. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Career Technical Education, 2008 November 13. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - National Governors Association Center for Best Practices, Forum on College and Career Readiness, 2008 May 12-13. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Advanced Study Strategies (VASS), 2007-2009. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - 2009 Virginia Rural Summit, 2009 September 14-15. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Ideas Portal-Top Ten Ideas, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Why Pre-K? Information Sheets, 2006-2007. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Virginia State Education Assistance Authority Concerns, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Reading and Literacy Partnership Committee Meeting, 2008 June 4. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Access Challenge Grant, SCHEV, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Sesquicentennial of the American Civil War Commission, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - 2006 Governor's Conference on Education, 2006 July 18. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB), Virginia Leadership Team Meeting, 2008 November 24. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Virginia School Boards Association Legislative Conference, 2009 February 12. (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2006-2009. (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Qualified Zone Academic Bond Program, 2006. (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Educational Leadership Group Tour to India, 2008. (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - National Governors Association (NGA) Grant, 2006. (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Capitol Flag Order, 26 April 2006. (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Return to Roots, Southwest Virginia, 2006. (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Appropriation Act, 2006. (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Campus Safety, 2007. (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Commission for the Arts, 2007. (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Virginia Department of Education, Governor's Report, 2009. (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Department of Education, Local Expenditures and Appropriations, 2009. (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Hopewell Public Schools, 2006. (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Arlington Public Schools, 2007. (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2006. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Subseries III.B. Files of Judy Heiman, Deputy Secretary of Education, 2003-2007 (bulk 2006)., Extent: 1.05 cubic feet (3 boxes).
    This subseries is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by subject. Judy Heiman served as Deputy Secretary of Education from January 2006 to December 2007. Heiman left the Kaine administration when she accepted a position in the California Legislative Analyst's Office. Prior to joining the Kaine administration, Heiman worked as budget and policy analyst for the Virginia Department of Planning and Budget. Additional Heiman records can be found in Subseries III.D. Files of Jean Bankos.
    Includes correspondence, reports, presentations, meeting agendas and notes, and decision briefs.
    - State Agencies
      - Virginia Commission for the Arts, 2007-2008. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Library of Virginia, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Cooperative Extension and the Agriculture Experiment Station, 2006 July 27. (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Southern Virginia Higher Education Center, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Schools for the Deaf and the Blind Consolidation, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - An Achievable Dream, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Autism Services, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of America, undated. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Career Education Foundation, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Council on Virginia's Future, 2005-2007. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Commonwealth Scholars Initiative, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correctional Education, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Comprehensive Services Act (CSA), 2006. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Council on Economic Education, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Education for a Lifetime, 2005-2006. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Educational Options, Inc., 2006. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Foster Care/Just Kids, undated. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Foster Care/Just Kids, 2005 and undated. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Office for Substance Abuse Prevention (GOSAP), 2005-2006. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Schools, 2003-2004; 2006. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - High Schools that Work and Making Middle Grades Work, 2006-2007. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Longwood University, Institute for Teaching Through Technology and Innovative Practices (ITTIP), 2006. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - National Assessment of Educational Progress (NAEP), undated. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Newsweek - Best High Schools, 2006 May 8. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - NASA Langley, 2005-2006. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - School Division Improvement Plan, Progress Report, 2006 February 14. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - The 2006 Virginia School Safety Survey Results (Draft), 2006 December. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Urban Policy Task Force, 2006 October 19. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Alliance of Family Child Care Associations, 2006. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Virtual Library of Virginia (VIVA), 2006. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Workforce Council, 2006. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III.C. Files of Dietra Trent, Deputy Secretary of Education, 2005-2009., Extent: 1.40 cubic feet (4 boxes).
    This subseries is housed in 4 boxes and is arranged roughly alphabetical. Dietra Trent served as Deputy Secretary of Education, Higher Education, from January 2006 to January 2010.
    Includes: Auditor of Public Accounts reports for education institutions, records related to the Civil Rights Memorial on Capitol Square, and Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) plans for higher education institutions.
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Reports, 2006-2008. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Science Museum of Virginia, 2006. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Reports, 2007-2009. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Reports, 2006; 2008-2009. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights Memorial, 2005-2006. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Carl D. Perkins Career and Technical Education Act of 2006, Virginia State Plan Review Committee, Notebook, 2007 (1 of 2). (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Carl D. Perkins Career and Technical Education Act of 2006, Virginia State Plan Review Committee, Notebook, 2007 (2 of 2). (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) Agenda Book, 2009 June 8. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - [Virginia] Attorney General's Government and Regulatory Reform Task Force, Final Report, 2009 June 11. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School, Virginia Modeling and Simulation Initiative (VIMSIM), Report, 2007 October 1. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - George Mason University, Edgemoor Building, 2007 (1 of 2). (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - George Mason University, Edgemoor Building, 2007 (2 of 2). (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Science Museum of Virginia, Belmont Bay Science Center, 2005 (1 of 2). (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Science Museum of Virginia, Belmont Bay Science Center, 2005 (2 of 2). (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Virginia State University, 2005-2006; 2008. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Virginia State University, Board of Visitors Meeting, 2007 April 12-13. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Year 07 Sole Source Fee Rebates to Institutions of Higher Education, 2008. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM)
      - Secretary of Education Agency SWAM Plans for Fiscal Years 2009 and 2010, 2008-2009. (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Blue Ridge Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Central Virginia Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Christopher Newport University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - College of William and Mary, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Danville Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Department of Education, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Eastern Shore Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Frontier Culture Museum, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - George Mason University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Germanna Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Gunston Hall, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - James Madison University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - John Tyler Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Longwood University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Mountain Empire Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - New River Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Norfolk State University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Northern Virginia Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Old Dominion University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Patrick Henry Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Piedmont Virginia Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Radford University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Rappahannock Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Richard Bland College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Science Museum of Virginia, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Southside Virginia Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - State Council of Higher Education, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - The Library of Virginia, 2009. (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Tidewater Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - University of Mary Washington, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - University of Virginia, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Virginia Commission for the Arts, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Virginia Commonwealth University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - Virginia Community College System, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Virginia Highlands Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Virginia Military Institute, 2008. (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Virginia School for the Deaf and the Blind, 2009. (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Virginia State University, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Virginia Western Community College, 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 48)
      - Wytheville Community College 2008-2009. (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Subseries III.D. Files of Jean Bankos, Senior Advisor to the Governor for Educational Projects, 2001-2002; 2004-2009 (bulk 2006-2009)., Extent: 3.35 cubic feet (4 boxes).
    This subseries is housed in 4 boxes. The briefing and meeting binders are arranged chronologically. The remainder of the files are in their original order. These files were from the office of Jean Bankos; however, they also contain records from Deputy Secretary of Education Judy Heiman. Jean Bankos served as Senior Advisor to the Governor for Educational Projects from June 2006 to June 2009.
    Subjects include: No Child Left Behind, Great Virginia Teach-In, Standards of Learning (SOLs), P-16 Education Council, Virginia Board of Education, Study of Truancy and School Dropout Prevention Advisory Group, and Virginia's National Governors Association Honor States Grant to Redesign the American High School.
    - Briefing and Meeting Binders
      - K-12 Overview of Public Education (1992-2000)-Judy Heiman's copy, undated. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - K-12 Overview of Public Education (1992-1993), undated. (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Mathematics Standards of Learning for Virginia Public Schools, 2002 (1 of 2). (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Mathematics Standards of Learning for Virginia Public Schools, 2002 (2 of 2). (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - English Standards of Learning, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Science Standards of Learning, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - P-16 Education Council Meeting Binder (Peter Blake's copy), 2005 November 22 (1 of 3). (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - P-16 Education Council Meeting Binder (Peter Blake's copy), 2005 November 22 (2 of 3). (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - P-16 Education Council Meeting Binder (Peter Blake's copy), 2005 November 22 (3 of 3). (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - The Great Virginia Teach-In: A Funding Proposal for 2007, by Virginia Dept. of Education, 2006 June 1. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - The 2007 Great Virginia Teach-In: A Call to Teach, 2007 March 17. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - National Center for Educational Accountability, Just for the Kids Annual Affiliate Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2006 June 14-15. (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - National Conference of State Legislatures, A Vision for Redesigned High Schools, Miami, Florida, 2007 October 18-19. (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Virginia Board of Education, Committees, 2006-2007
        - Working Meeting of the Board of Education and Governor Timothy M. Kaine, 2006 October 24. (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - School and Division Accountability Committee, 2006 September 26. (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - School and Division Accountability Committee, 2007 September 25. (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Early Childhood Committee, 2006 September 26. (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Early Childhood Committee, 2006 October 24. (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Early Childhood Committee, 2007 February 27. (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Literacy Committee, 2006 September 26. (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Literacy Committee, 2006 October 24. (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Literacy Committee, 2007 February 27. (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Graduation and Dropout Committee, 2006 October 25. (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Graduation and Dropout Committee, 2007 January 10. (Box 25, Folder 13)